bollywoodshaadis.com 2018-05-23

# Privacy Policy

You consent to the use of your personal information by BollywoodShaadis.com and/or its third party providers and distributors in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy. BollywoodShaadis.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with us under extremely strict confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from BollywoodShaadis.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name, contact number, address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to participate on the site, forum, contests, use of softwares, articles, white papers or to provide you with a subscription. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information.

We may share your information with its business partners who sponsor an event, white paper downloads, contest, or promotion; or who jointly offer a service or feature with us.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender email id with details of the correction requested.

We may, if you so choose, send direct mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to ‘opt-out’ of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose to not receive such mailers, we will take all steps to remove you from the list.

We transfer information about you if BollywoodShaadis.com is acquired by or merged with another company.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

If you are a copyright owner any image/picture used on our site and you believe the use of your images on this site is infringing in any way, please contact us immediately by sending an email to **legal@bollywoodshaadis.com**. We will promptly comply with any takedown demand.

BollywoodShaadis.com reserves the right to use the information to provide the user a more personalized online experience. BollywoodShaadis.com provides links to web sites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You agree that BollywoodShaadis.com is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third party web sites. The User is requested to peruse the policies posted by other web sites regarding privacy and other topics before use.

BollywoodShaadis.com is not responsible for third party content accessible through the site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and user shall bear all risks associated with the use of such content. BollywoodShaadis.com is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort user may incur from dealing with any third party.

If you have more question please visit contact us section.
